<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>@da_nn_y_o</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2019-07-11T17:47:14-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name>Daniel Denenberg</name>
   <email>dannydenenberg@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Linear Algebra; The How and Why 🤨</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/linear-algebra"/>
   <updated>2019-07-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/linear-al</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article aims to give the reader an understanding of the linear algebra aspect of mathematics one needs to know to start programming or developing machine/deep learning models and gain an understanding of them. Each section corresponds to a unique linear algebra operation. I hope this paper is easy to read and understand to a person who has just a basic high school level understanding of mathematics. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;dimensions&quot;&gt;Dimensions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, what the heck is a matrix? Well, a matrix is a “rectangular array of numbers”. In simpler terms, a matrix is a grid where each square holds a value. You might be familiar with matrices in programming (also known as an “array of arrays”). In Java, for example, to create a matrix, you might type this: &lt;code&gt;int[][] mat = new int[2][2]&lt;/code&gt;. This would initialize a “2 by 2” matrix. Here is an example of a “2 by 2” matrix in math:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{ll}{2} &amp;amp; {4} \\ {1} &amp;amp; {3}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Above is a “matrix of numbers”. Why did I call it “2 by 2”? It has 2 rows and 2 columns. So, for example, this matrix would be a “3 by 2” or just 3x2:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1} &amp;amp; {2} \\ {3} &amp;amp; {4} \\ {5} &amp;amp; {6}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the symbol commonly used to represent matrix dimensions is the all-real-numbers symbol: \(\mathbb{R}\). The dimensions of the previous example could be written as  \(\mathbb{R}^{3 \times 2}\)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;indexing&quot;&gt;Indexing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another very common operation needed to be performed on matrices is “indexing”. This is where you can get one value from a matrix. So, if I call the &lt;code&gt;3x2&lt;/code&gt; matrix above \(A\) , and I wanted to index the first element (1), I would say \(A_{11}\). The reason I do this is because matrix indexing occurs by a subscript where the first number corresponds to the row and the second number corresponds the column of the element in the matrix you want to get (eg. \(Nameofmatrix_{rowcol}\)). Another example: let's suppose I want to index the 6 in the matrix above. It is in the 3rd row and 2nd column, so to index it I would say \(A_{32}\) (Assuming my matrix was called \(A\)).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;vectors&quot;&gt;Vectors&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A “vector” is just a matrix but with one column &lt;u&gt;only&lt;/u&gt;. You could say it is an &lt;code&gt;n x 1&lt;/code&gt; matrix because it can have as many rows (n) but only one column. When indexing a vector, you only need one number in the subscript and that corresponds to the row of the number you are indexing. So, if we have this vector&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$Y=\left[\begin{array}{l}{1} \\ {2} \\ {3}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;then, \(Y_{1}=1\), \(Y_{2}=2\), and \(Y_{3}=3\). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Just a quick note: all the indexing I have written on is what is called “1-indexing” because the first value in the matrix is referred to with a 1. If you are familiar with programming, then you will most likely be familiar with zero-indexing, where the first value in an array (or matrix) is the 0th element. 1-indexed vectors/matrices are the &lt;u&gt;most common&lt;/u&gt;. Another note: matrices and vectors are often named using CAPITOL lettering by convention.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;simple-operations&quot;&gt;Simple Operations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now we will start to perform operations on matrices. For each simple operator (add, subtract, multiply, divide) there are two different matrix operations associated. The two matrix operations are known as “scalar” and “element-wise”. The scalar operator takes a number and performs one operation with each element in the matrix. For example,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$3+\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1} &amp;amp; {2} \\ {3} &amp;amp; {4}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1+3} &amp;amp; {2+3} \\ {3+3} &amp;amp; {4+3}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{ll}{4} &amp;amp; {5} \\ {6} &amp;amp; {7}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This works the same way for subtraction, multiplication, and division using scalar values. With element wise operations, you take two matrices of the SAME dimensions and perform one operation with each corresponding element in each matrix. For example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1} &amp;amp; {2} \\ {3} &amp;amp; {4}\end{array}\right] *\left[\begin{array}{ll}{5} &amp;amp; {4} \\ {3} &amp;amp; {2}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1 * 5} &amp;amp; {2 * 4} \\ {3 * 3} &amp;amp; {4 * 2}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{ll}{4} &amp;amp; {8} \\ {9} &amp;amp; {8}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is an example where you can't perform the element-wise operation because the two matrices do NOT have the same dimensions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{ll}{2} &amp;amp; {3} \\ {4} &amp;amp; {5}\end{array}\right]+\left[\begin{array}{lll}{1} &amp;amp; {2} &amp;amp; {3} \\ {4} &amp;amp; {5} &amp;amp; {6}\end{array}\right]=undefined$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;matrix-vector-multiplication&quot;&gt;Matrix-Vector Multiplication&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When multiplying a matrix by a vector, you take each row of the matrix and multiply each element of that row with the corresponding element in the vector and then add them. You do that for each row in the matrix and you end up with a vector with the number of rows as the original matrix. This is known as the &lt;strong&gt;“dot product”&lt;/strong&gt; and is represented with this symbol: “\(\otimes\)&quot; (or with no symbol like 2x means to multiply 2 with x). It will make more sense once you see this example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1} &amp;amp; {3} \\ {4} &amp;amp; {0} \\ {2} &amp;amp; {1}\end{array}\right] \otimes\left[\begin{array}{l}{1} \\ {5}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{l}{?} \\ {?} \\ {?}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To perform the dot product, we first take the first row of the matrix, \(\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1} &amp;amp; {3}\end{array}\right]\), and multiply each element in it with the corresponding element in the vector like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1} &amp;amp; {3}\end{array}\right] *\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1} &amp;amp; {5}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{lll}{1 * 1} &amp;amp; {3 * 5}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1} &amp;amp; {15}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now you add the values up, \(1+15=16\). This becomes the first value in the resulting matrix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1} &amp;amp; {3} \\ {4} &amp;amp; {0} \\ {2} &amp;amp; {1}\end{array}\right] \otimes\left[\begin{array}{l}{1} \\ {5}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{c}{16} \\ {?} \\ {?}\end{array}\right]$$	&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You now perform these same steps with the rest of the rows in the matrix. For the sake of brevity, I will put the final operations in the matrix:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{ll}{1} &amp;amp; {3} \\ {4} &amp;amp; {0} \\ {2} &amp;amp; {1}\end{array}\right] \otimes\left[\begin{array}{l}{1} \\ {5}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{c}{16} \\ {(4 * 1+0 * 5)} \\ {(2 * 1+1 * 5)}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{c}{16} \\ {4} \\ {7}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that final matrix is the answer. It's not difficult to understand, just tedious to execute. This is why NO ONE does this by hand, we use computers to do this for us. In python, using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.numpy.org/&quot;&gt;numpy&lt;/a&gt; library, you can just say this to perform that entire dot product: &lt;code&gt;numpy.dot(matrix_A, matrix_B)&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, because the operations for dot product are so specific, you cannot perform them with just two randomly dimensioned matrices, they have to be specific as well. If the matrix has dimensions \(\mathbb{R}^{m\times n}\) (\(m\) rows, \(n\) columns), then the vector must have the dimensions \(\mathbb{R}^{n\times 1}\) (n dimensional vector). The answer would then be a vector with the dimensions \(\mathbb{R}^{m \times 1}\).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;matrix-matrix-multiplication&quot;&gt;Matrix-Matrix Multiplication&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To multiply a matrix &lt;strong&gt;by another matrix&lt;/strong&gt; we need to do the &lt;strong&gt;&quot;dot product&quot;&lt;/strong&gt; of the rows and columns ... what does that mean? Well, in the previous section, we took a matrix and a vector, and for each row in the matrix, we found the dot product of that row with the vector and ended up with a vector as the result. For multiplying matrices, you do that EXACT same thing, but repeat it for each column in the second matrix acting as individual vectors. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will make more sense in an example. To work out the answer for the &lt;strong&gt;1st row &lt;/strong&gt;and&lt;strong&gt; 1st column&lt;/strong&gt; of the resulting matrix in this problem, I would find the dot product of the &lt;strong&gt;1st row &lt;/strong&gt;of the first matrix and the&lt;strong&gt; 1st column &lt;/strong&gt;of the second matrix like so: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{lll}\color{blue}{1} &amp;amp; \color{blue}{2} &amp;amp; \color{blue}{3} \\ {4} &amp;amp; {5} &amp;amp; {6}\end{array}\right] \times\left[\begin{array}{cc}\color{blue}{7} &amp;amp; {8} \\ \color{blue}{9} &amp;amp; {10} \\ \color{blue}{11} &amp;amp; {12}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{c}\color{blue}{58} &amp;amp; {}\\ {} &amp;amp;{}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\begin{aligned}(1,2,3) \otimes(7,9,11) &amp;amp;=1 \times 7+2 \times 9+3 \times 11 \\ &amp;amp;=58 \end{aligned}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To work out the answer for the &lt;strong&gt;2nd row &lt;/strong&gt;and&lt;strong&gt; 1st column &lt;/strong&gt;of the resulting matrix, I would find the dot product of the &lt;strong&gt;2nd row&lt;/strong&gt; of the first matrix and the &lt;strong&gt;1st column &lt;/strong&gt;of the second like so:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{lll}{1} &amp;amp; {2} &amp;amp;{3} \\ \color{blue}{4} &amp;amp; \color {blue}{5} &amp;amp; \color {blue}{6}\end{array}\right] \times\left[\begin{array}{cc}\color{blue}{7} &amp;amp; {8} \\ \color{blue}{9} &amp;amp; {10} \\ \color{blue}{11} &amp;amp; {12}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{c} {58} &amp;amp; {}\\ \color{blue}{139} &amp;amp; {}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\begin{aligned}(4,5,6) \otimes(7,9,11) &amp;amp;=4 \times 7+5 \times 9+6 \times 11 \\ &amp;amp;=139 \end{aligned}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can do the same thing for the &lt;strong&gt;1st row &lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;2nd column:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\begin{aligned}(1,2,3) \otimes(8,10,12) &amp;amp;=1 \times 8+2 \times 10+3 \times 12 \\ &amp;amp;=64 \end{aligned}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And for the &lt;strong&gt;2nd row &lt;/strong&gt;and &lt;strong&gt;2nd column: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\begin{aligned}(4,5,6) \otimes(8,10,12) &amp;amp;=4 \times 8+5 \times 10+6 \times 12 \\ &amp;amp;=154 \end{aligned}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And finally, we get:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\left[\begin{array}{lll}{1} &amp;amp; {2} &amp;amp; {3} \\ {4} &amp;amp; {5} &amp;amp; {6}\end{array}\right] \times\left[\begin{array}{cc}{7} &amp;amp; {8} \\ {9} &amp;amp; {10} \\ {11} &amp;amp; {12}\end{array}\right]=\left[\begin{array}{cc}{58} &amp;amp; {64} \\ {139} &amp;amp; {154}\end{array}\right]$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-why&quot;&gt;The Why&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why is this important to know?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, to be honest if you aren't doing something related to mathematics or computer science (machine learning) I would struggle to give you a good reason that you need to know it. But, for machine learning, it is EXTREMELY useful. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When modeling the layers of a neural network in a program on a computer, each layer can be represented by a vector and the weights as a matrix. Then, when it comes time to forward propagate, the next layer of the network is calculated by the dot product of the previous layer (the vector) and the weights. There are actually many cloud computing services that have computers you can access that are specially designed to be able to perform matrix operations quickly which greatly improves the training process for a network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is all I got for this one! Please feel free to email me with any questions 👍📬&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How to create a Ghost blog with docker 🐳+ AWS ❤️</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/ghost-blog-aws-docker"/>
   <updated>2019-06-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/docker-and-aws</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Login to the AWS website&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click on Services  (top bar)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click on EC2&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click on Launch Instance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Search and choose Ubuntu Server (18 or up)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leave selected the free tear (unless you have upwards of $10000000000)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Edit security groups (by clicking on &lt;code&gt;edit security groups&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click Add rule - &lt;code&gt;http&lt;/code&gt; - leave other defaults&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click Add rule - &lt;code&gt;https&lt;/code&gt; -leave other defaults&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click Launch Instance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choose Create new pair key from the drop down selector (name it and download it)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Open terminal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CD into the directory where the pair key was downloaded to and do this&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Change the .pem file permissions with: &lt;code&gt;sudo chmod 600 &amp;lt;&amp;lt;MYPAIRKEYFILENAME&amp;gt;&amp;gt;.pem&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go to your AWS instances tab in the EC2 page and find the Public DNS (IPv4) of your instance &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;ssh &lt;a href=&quot;/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7c091e091208093c191f4e514948514e4e48514d4f4e51454f521f13110c090819514d521d111d0613121d0b0f521f1311&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;__cf_email__&quot; data-cfemail=&quot;790c1b0c170d0c39&quot;&gt;[email&amp;#160;protected]&lt;/span&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;lt;INSERT.Public.Dns.IPv4&amp;gt;&amp;gt; -i PairKeyName.pem&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Type &lt;code&gt;yes&lt;/code&gt; to get into the ubuntu computer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Install docker: &lt;code&gt;sudo snap install docker&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make a start file: &lt;code&gt;vim startserver&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Put this in the script👇: &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;#!/bin/bash; docker run -d --name website -e url=https://&amp;lt;&amp;lt;websitename&amp;gt;&amp;gt; -p 80:2386 -v /home/ubuntu/website:/var/lib/ghost/content ghost&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create a /website directory: &lt;code&gt;mkdir website&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go to &lt;code&gt;cloudflare.com&lt;/code&gt; and link your website to it by creating an account (or signing in) and going through the steps to link it to your URL that you used in step &lt;strong&gt;21&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make a &lt;code&gt;CNAME&lt;/code&gt; record with the name being &lt;code&gt;@&lt;/code&gt; and the address being the public IPv4 of the aws instance that you found in step &lt;strong&gt;15&lt;/strong&gt; (example: &lt;code&gt;ec2-54-224-132-93.compute-1.amazonaws.com&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go to your domain service (mine is google domains) and set the nameservers to be cloudflare’s (you should have already done this step while setting up cloudflare in step &lt;strong&gt;23&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Change the permissions of the &lt;code&gt;startserver&lt;/code&gt; script to be able to execute: &lt;code&gt;chmod +x startscript&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now run it: &lt;code&gt;./startscript&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It will take a bit to complete because docker needs to pull the image off of their website, but when it does everything should be up and running&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;please-note&quot;&gt;Please Note&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It may take a bit for cloudflare to enable https. It will also take some time for your domain provider to change its nameservers and for that change to propagate back to cloudflare.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How to contribute on GitHub</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/contributing"/>
   <updated>2019-04-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/git-contributing</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This guide assumes that you have a &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt; account and &lt;a href=&quot;https://git-scm.com/book/en/v2/Getting-Started-Installing-Git&quot;&gt;git installed&lt;/a&gt; on your machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-1-fork&quot;&gt;Step 1: Fork&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you find a repo that looks cool, the first step is to fork it. A fork will create a copy of the repo under your account that you can modify, while maintaining a link to original (that’s called the upstream repo).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/forking.png&quot; alt=&quot;Forking&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-2-clone&quot;&gt;Step 2: Clone&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s download the code to your local machine by cloning the fork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;git clone &amp;lt;your-fork-url.git&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should now have a directory for your project that can be opened with your &lt;a href=&quot;https://code.visualstudio.com/&quot;&gt;preferred code editor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-3-branch&quot;&gt;Step 3: Branch&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A git repo is just a big tree 🌳. You might have hundreds of people working on the same project and branches ensure that collaboration can happen without complete chaos. Changes on your branch are isolated from the work everybody else is doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;git checkout -b my-cool-thing
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point you can start making changes to the code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-4-commit&quot;&gt;Step 4: Commit&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you are happy with the changes, you can stage the changes and commit the code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;git add .
git commit -m &quot;🚀 I made this software better!&quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-5-pull-request&quot;&gt;Step 5: Pull Request&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A “pull request” is identical to a “git merge”, but it is requested from an external source - you. In fact, it is called a “merge request” on other platforms, which I think is a better name, but I digress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s push your branch to your fork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;git push origin my-cool-thing
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you go back to Github you should automatically see a button labeled &lt;strong&gt;Create New Pull Request for my-cool-thing&lt;/strong&gt;. Go ahead and push that button. Add additional details as needed and it will show up in the list of PRs once submitted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many larger projects have their own “Contributor Guidelines” and may require you to sign a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Contributor_License_Agreement&quot;&gt;CLA&lt;/a&gt; before participating.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How to install Node.js</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/installing-node"/>
   <updated>2019-03-14T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/installing-node</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It is likely that you already have &lt;a href=&quot;https://nodejs.org/en/&quot;&gt;NodeJS&lt;/a&gt; installed on your machine. Try running &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;node -v&lt;/code&gt; from the command line. If that does not work or the version is older than &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;8.15&lt;/code&gt;, follow the install instructions below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;node-version-manager-nvm&quot;&gt;Node Version Manager NVM&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/creationix/nvm&quot;&gt;Node Version Manager&lt;/a&gt; NVM makes it easy to switch between Node versions in your local environment. I highly recommend using it over the native install on your system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;mac-and-linux&quot;&gt;Mac and Linux&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply run the install script from the command line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;curl &lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;-o-&lt;/span&gt; https://raw.githubusercontent.com/creationix/nvm/v0.33.11/install.sh | bash
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Restart your terminal. You should now be able to easily install and manage Node versions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;nvm install 10

nvm use 10
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;windows&quot;&gt;Windows&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NVM is not available on Windows, but there is a solid alternative with &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/coreybutler/nvm-windows&quot;&gt;nvm-windows&lt;/a&gt;. It provides an installer than you can download from the repo. Once installed you will have access commands similar to those above.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What the heck is a perceptron? 🥗</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/what-is-a-perceptron"/>
   <updated>2019-02-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/perceptron</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A quick article about what a perceptron is, how it works, and why it is important.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In short, the perceptron is an algorithm. A very simple one at that. &lt;br /&gt;The algorithm it performs, in machine learning lingo, is known as &lt;em&gt;binary classification&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binary classification&lt;/strong&gt; is the task of classifying elements into two groups. Hence the word binary — meaning 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the algorithm does, it &lt;strong&gt;take an input and produce an output&lt;/strong&gt;. The method by which the perceptron produces an output is called the &lt;em&gt;weighted sum&lt;/em&gt;. It takes some input X, multiplies it by some weight W, adds in a bias B and then runs that value through some &lt;em&gt;step function&lt;/em&gt; which classifies the weighted sum as a 0 or 1 (most of the time).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;If there are multiple inputs, then there is a single weight assigned to each input and all of the inputs are multiplied by their corresponding weight and then summed together and added to the bias before being passed through the step function.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is visual of what a simple perceptron with &lt;em&gt;n&lt;/em&gt; inputs may look like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-begin: image--&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.denenberg.info/content/images/downloaded_images/What-the-heck-is-a-perceptron-/1-vn7VIPb_JpwEX7PAftjYsw.png&quot; class=&quot;kg-image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: image--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This image depicts the inputs (represented as subscripts of X) each being multiplied by their corresponding weights, summed together, and passed through some step function that takes the weighted sum and produces either a 0 or a 1. Notice that there is a constant that is fed into the perceptron as well as the other inputs. This constant will always be 1 and when multiplied with the first weight, represents the bias. So, essentially, that weight is the bias — it is added to the sum of the weights &lt;em&gt;without &lt;/em&gt;being multiplied first with an input.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A simple step function is depicted below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-begin: image--&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.denenberg.info/content/images/downloaded_images/What-the-heck-is-a-perceptron-/1-6K2w2TpQmHyphnv5fSvxUg.png&quot; class=&quot;kg-image&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Unit Step Function&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: image--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This step function takes some value. If the value is greater than or equal to 0, then it outputs 1, otherwise, it outputs 0.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-is-it-useful-at-classifying-things&quot;&gt;How is it useful at classifying things?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The perceptron is a subset of machine learning algorithms known as supervised learning. This means that when you teach a perceptron to learn to classify inputs into 2 categories, you give it the inputs and the labels that you want the perceptron to produce in the end (0 or 1 for binary classification, usually).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The perceptron initializes its weights randomly and get’s fed the inputs. It takes its final output from the step function and compares it to the label that you gave it for the specified set of inputs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The perceptron can then see whether it was wrong at all and how wrong. It can quantify how wrong it is by producing a loss function which takes the perceptron’s output and the target label provided by you and produces a number. In essence, the loss function is saying, “this perceptron is 2.76 wrong” or “this perceptron is 8.92 wrong”, etc. Here is a common loss function for binary classification known as Squared Error:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$Loss=(predicted-target)^2$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, in a simple example, if the perceptron was fed inputs and produced a 1, but the label assigned to the inputs was 0, then the loss of the perceptron would be:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$Loss=(1-0)^2=1$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The perceptron in this case was “1 wrong”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;It can then use this value to adjust the weights is various ways, one of which is known as &lt;strong&gt;Gradient Descent&lt;/strong&gt;. In GD, you adjust the weights by subtracting the partial derivative of the loss function with respect to each weight. To actually figure out the derivatives, you would use the chain rule because the loss function is in actuality a composition of the weighted sum plus the bias, piped through the step function:&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{\partial Loss}{\partial w_i}=\frac{\partial Loss}{\partial y}\frac{\partial y}{\partial w_i}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;If you are familiar with Calculus and derivatives, this concept shouldn’t be too difficult to understand and I am planning on writing an article on this soon. But it is beyond the scope of this high-level paper.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-a-binary-classifier&quot;&gt;What is a Binary Classifier?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This means that the input entered is mapped to 2 different categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another way to describe this is by saying that the information entered into a perceptron is linearly separable:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-begin: image--&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.denenberg.info/content/images/downloaded_images/What-the-heck-is-a-perceptron-/1-2Y9fKZBzQprHaNGKEEePmw.png&quot; class=&quot;kg-image&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Linearly Separable&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: image--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This means that the input entered can be separated by a&lt;strong&gt; single line.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-perceptron-is-just-like-a-linear-function&quot;&gt;A perceptron is just like a linear function&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing to note about a perceptron is that it is functions kind of line a linear function. For example, here is a function in slope-intercept form:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$y=mx+b$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When comparing this to a perceptron you can see they are much alike. The X is the input, the m is the weight, and the b is the bias. Here is what the perceptron value before it is run through the step function would look like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$y=\sum_{i=0}^{n} X_{i} W_{i}+B$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looks pretty similar, huh?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This high level overview of a perceptron is a good prep for learning about &lt;strong&gt;Neural Networks&lt;/strong&gt; which are just perceptrons stacked on top of each other and gathered into layers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just keep learning!

&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Derivative of Sigmoid ✍️</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/derivative-sigmoid"/>
   <updated>2019-01-25T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/sigmoid</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em id=&quot;a-comprehensive-walk-through-of-taking-the-derivative-of-the-sigmoid-function-&quot;&gt;A comprehensive walk-through of taking the derivative of the sigmoid function.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;One of the most frequently used activation functions in machine learning, or more specifically, neural networks is the sigmoid function. In the backpropagation step in training a neural network, you have to find the derivative of the loss function with respect to each weight in the network. To do this, you have to find the derivative of your activation function. This article aims to clear up any confusion about finding the derivative of the sigmoid function.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To begin, here is the sigmoid function:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\sigma(x)=\frac{1}{1+e^{-x}}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a test, take the sigmoid of 5 on your calculator. You should get 0.99330714907.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the purposes of the derivative, this function can also be written as:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\sigma(x)=(1+e^{-x})^{-1}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-impressions&quot;&gt;First Impressions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first thing I noticed about this function, is that it is a composition of functions. The first function being&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\sigma(x)=(m)^{-1}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and the second being&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$m=1+e^{-x}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recall that in Calculus, when there is a composition of functions, the derivative, is the first function with respect to the second multiplied by the second function with respect to the variable, in this case &lt;em&gt;x.&lt;/em&gt; Like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{d\sigma}{dx}=\frac{d\sigma}{dm}\frac{dm}{dx}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, the derivative of the sigmoid with respect to &lt;em&gt;x&lt;/em&gt; is the derivative of the sigmoid function with respect to &lt;em&gt;m&lt;/em&gt; times the derivative of &lt;em&gt;m&lt;/em&gt; with respect to &lt;em&gt;x&lt;/em&gt;. You can think of this function composition rule as a kind of intermediate computation that results in the original derivative that you wanted by cross cancelation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{d\sigma}{dx}=\frac{d\sigma}{\xcancel{dm}}\frac{\xcancel{dm}}{dx}=\frac{d\sigma}{dx}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that we know the sigmoid function is a composition of functions, all we have to do to find the derivative, is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Find the derivative of the sigmoid function with respect to &lt;em&gt;m&lt;/em&gt;, our intermediate value&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Find the derivative of &lt;em&gt;m&lt;/em&gt; with respect to &lt;em&gt;x&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Multiply those values together&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-derivative-of-the-sigmoid-with-respect-to-m&quot;&gt;1. Derivative of the sigmoid with respect to m&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s look back to what the sigmoid function looks like with &lt;em&gt;m&lt;/em&gt; as our intermediate value:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\sigma(x)=(m)^{-1}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find the derivative of this with respect to &lt;em&gt;m&lt;/em&gt; is fairly simple if we can remember the power rule:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{d(x^n)}{dx}=n\times x^{n-1}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;em&gt;The derivative of &lt;/em&gt;x^n&lt;em&gt; is &lt;/em&gt;n&lt;em&gt; times the derivative of &lt;/em&gt;x&lt;em&gt; to the power of &lt;/em&gt;n-1&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{d(x^n)}{dx}=-1\times m^{-1-1}=-m^{-2}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, if we substitute our original value of &lt;em&gt;m&lt;/em&gt; back into the equation, we get&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$-m^{-2}=-(1+e^{-x})^{-2}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{d\sigma}{dm}=-(1+e^{-x})^{-2}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yay! We completed step 1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-find-the-derivative-of-m-with-respect-to-x&quot;&gt;2. Find the derivative of m with respect to x&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s m:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$m=1+e^{-x}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find the derivative, we have to find the derivative of each term with respect to &lt;em&gt;x. &lt;/em&gt;The first term is easy:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{d(1)}{dx}=0$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second term is a bit more complicated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s let&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$y=e^u$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$u=-x$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We know that&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{dy}{du}=e^u     \\      \frac{du}{dx}=-1$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If getting to &lt;em&gt;e^u &lt;/em&gt;is not clear, please read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.themathpage.com/aCalc/exponential.htm&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, using the chain rule once again,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{dy}{dx}=\frac{dy}{du}\frac{du}{dx}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, we just multiply those derivatives we just calculated to get the derivative with respect to &lt;em&gt;x:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{dy}{dx}=e^u \times (-1)=-e^u=-e^{-x}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all for step 2,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{dm}{dx}=-e^{-x}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-multiply-the-derivatives&quot;&gt;3. Multiply the derivatives&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recall, that once we found the two intermediate derivatives, we had to multiply them. So, here is a quick summary:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{d\sigma}{dx}=\frac{d\sigma}{dm}\frac{dm}{dx}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{d\sigma}{dm}=-(1+e^{-x})^{-2}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{dm}{dx}=-e^{-x}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, if you remember how to multiply :), we can finally finish this!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{d\sigma}{dx}=-(1+e^{-x})^{-2} \times -e^{-x}=\frac{e^{-x}}{(1+e^{-x})^2}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can now take this value and use it as the derivation of the sigmoid function. An interesting thing occurs after you manipulate this result, though. It turns out that you can rewrite the derivative like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{d\sigma}{dx}=\sigma(x)(1-\sigma(x))$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The derivative of sigma is the sigma times 1 minus the sigma. Wow. I feel cheated. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you even remotely enjoyed this article, keep learning about AI and deep learning! 👍

&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>🧮 The Squeeze Theorem and Why I like it</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/squeeze-theorem"/>
   <updated>2018-11-22T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/squeeze-theorem</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An intuitive explanation of an awesome theorem.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I was studying calculus, I came across this statement:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\lim _{\theta \rightarrow 0} \frac{\sin \theta}{\theta}=1$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This amazed my because of the fact that sin of 0 is 0, so with substitution of theta in the fraction next to the limit, it would end up as 0/0 or undefined. Now, I had already studied limits a bit and knew about l’hopital’s rule. So, I proceeded to take the derivative of the top and bottom of the fraction with respect to theta and checked out what I got. This got me to the expected answer of 1/1 = 1 because the derivative of sin(x) is cos(x) and cos(0) is 1. Now this was all fine and dandy, but as I did more research into the limit listed above, I found a theorem called The Squeeze Theorem which I thought was a much more fun way to solve this same problem. This article is my shot at fully explaining the proof that accompanies the limit shown above using the Squeeze Theorem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-proof&quot;&gt;The Proof&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To begin, take a look at this picture of a few triangles drawn using different points around a unit circle. If you don’t already know, a unit circle is one with a radius of 1. The point A is at (0,0), point C is at some point on the edge of the circle, point D is at (1,0), and point E is at some point (1, x).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-begin: image--&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.denenberg.info/content/images/downloaded_images/The-Squeeze-Theorem-and-Why-I-like-it/1-5gctWhTjU8-tO_15qQccHQ.png&quot; class=&quot;kg-image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: image--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using this visual, let us compare the &lt;strong&gt;areas&lt;/strong&gt; of two triangles and a sector.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$△ACD \le ⌔ACD \le △AED$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can see that this is true by just looking at the graph. Next, I will define the values of the &lt;strong&gt;areas&lt;/strong&gt;. Note that theta will refer to the angle made on the unit circle with each of the shapes (the bottom left angle of the triangle or sector).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\begin{array}{c}{\triangle ACD=\frac{1}{2} b h=\frac{1}{2} \cdot 1 \cdot \sin \theta=\frac{\sin \theta}{2}} \\ {⌔ACD=\frac{1}{2} r^{2} \theta=\frac{1}{2} \cdot 1^{2} \cdot \theta=\frac{\theta}{2}} \\ {\triangle AED=\frac{1}{2} b h=\frac{1}{2} \cdot 1 \cdot \tan \theta=\frac{\tan \theta}{2}}\end{array}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just FYI, the hight of triangle △AED is tan(x) because tan(x) is opposite over adjacent and adjacent is 1, so it is really just &lt;strong&gt;the side opposite the angle&lt;/strong&gt;, which is the hight. (That confused me at first too 😂)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that we have this, we can re-compare (is that a word?) the areas using actual values.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\frac{\sin \theta}{2} \leq \frac{\theta}{2} \leq \frac{\tan \theta}{2}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, I am going to perform a set of operation to all of the elements in the inequality. This is legal as it preserves the &lt;em&gt;truthfulness&lt;/em&gt; of the inequality like applying the same operation to each side of an equals sign preserves the equality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, I will multiply each element by 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\sin \theta \leq \theta \leq \tan \theta$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second, I will divide by sin(𝜃).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$1 \leq \frac{\theta}{\sin \theta} \leq \frac{1}{\cos \theta}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I will take the reciprocal of each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$1 \geq \frac{\sin \theta}{\theta} \geq \cos \theta$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These reciprocals will get us to the final result that we want. All we have to do now is take the limit as listed at the top and analyze the results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\begin{array}{c}{\lim _{\theta \rightarrow 0}\left[1 \geq \frac{\sin \theta}{\theta} \geq \cos \theta\right]} \\ {\lim _{\theta \rightarrow 0}\left[1 \geq \frac{\sin \theta}{\theta} \geq 1\right]} \\ {1 \geq \lim _{\theta \rightarrow 0} \frac{\sin \theta}{\theta} \geq 1}\end{array}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you can most likely see (I highlighted it), by substitution of the limit value into each element of the inequality, we get 1 is greater than or equal to the limit of sin theta over theta as theta approaches 0 which is greater than or equal to 1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because we know this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\begin{array}{c}{\text {if}} \\ {1 \geq x \geq 1} \\ {\text {then,}} \\{x=1}\end{array}$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now we can say that the limit of sin of theta over theta as theta approaches 0 &lt;strong&gt;has to be 1&lt;/strong&gt; because of what I just stated above. Kinda cool, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I loved learning about the squeeze theorem more than others just because of all of the steps involved in getting to the final solution. It was a giant puzzle and a journey! This is just one reason of many why math is &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;fun and intuitive.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please stay tuned for more and clap as your heart desires 👏

&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Setting up an Apache server on a Raspberry Pi</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/apache-server"/>
   <updated>2018-06-17T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/apache-server</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;contents&quot;&gt;Contents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#install-apache&quot;&gt;Install apache&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#test-the-web-server&quot;&gt;Test the web server&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#changing-the-default-page&quot;&gt;Changing the default page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#install-php-if-you-want&quot;&gt;Install PHP (If you want)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#making-it-public&quot;&gt;Making it public&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#port-forwarding&quot;&gt;Port forwarding&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#test-the-web-server-part-2&quot;&gt;Test the web server (part 2)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;install-apache&quot;&gt;Install apache&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Install apache. Head into terminal and update the available packages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo apt-get update
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Then, install apache2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo apt-get install apache2 -y
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;test-the-web-server&quot;&gt;Test the web server&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By default, Apache puts a test HTML file in the web folder. This default web page is served when you browse to http://localhost/ on the pi itself, or http://192.168.0.6 (whatever the pi’s internal ip address is) from another computer on the local network. To find the pi’s ip address, type &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;hostname -I&lt;/code&gt; at the terminal. Learn more about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raspberrypi.org/documentation/remote-access/ip-address.md&quot;&gt;finding IP’s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The default page will look something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://assets.digitalocean.com/articles/lamp-debian8/JUGu5aW.png&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;The default web page apache gives us&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you see this, you have apache working!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;changing-the-default-page&quot;&gt;Changing the default page&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This default web page is an HTML file on the filesystem. It is located at &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/var/www/html/index.html&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Navigate to this directory in terminal and see what is in there:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ cd /var/www/html
$ ls -al
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will spit out:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;total 12
drwxr-xr-x  2 root root 4096 Jan  8 01:29 .
drwxr-xr-x 12 root root 4096 Jan  8 01:28 ..
-rw-r--r--  1 root root  177 Jan  8 01:29 index.html
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means that there is one file in /var/www/html/ called &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;index.html&lt;/code&gt; and is owned by the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;root&lt;/code&gt; user. In order to edit the file, you have to change ownership. You could use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;sudo&lt;/code&gt;. Like this: &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;sudo chown pi: index.html&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, if you want to put files in your website, you can place them in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/var/www/html&lt;/code&gt; folder!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;install-php-if-you-want&quot;&gt;Install PHP (If you want)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go into terminal and type:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo apt-get install php libapache2-mod-php -y
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, you can run php from your server. We are going to try it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go into the web folder where &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;index.html&lt;/code&gt; is stored (&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/var/www/html&lt;/code&gt;) and remove the index by typing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo rm index.html
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, we are going to create an index for our site in php. Create and edit a new index:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo nano index.php
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;NOTE: nano is a text editor install on all raspberry pi’s&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put some PHP in it (we’ll make it dynamic):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-php highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;?php&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;echo&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;hello world. Today is &quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;date&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Y-m-d H:i:s'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;?&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;making-it-public&quot;&gt;Making it public&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will explain how others can access your web site through port forwarding and your IPv4 address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to terminal. If you type &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ifconfig&lt;/code&gt; and press enter, you will get something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;pi@raspberrypi:~ $ ifconfig
eth0      Link encap:Ethernet  HWaddr b8:27:eb:96:cc:5a
          inet addr:192.168.0.10  Bcast:192.168.0.255  Mask:255.255.255.0
          inet6 addr: fe80::bb8e:9610:ab7b:7ae5/64 Scope:Link
          inet6 addr: 2600:8804:1e80:6e30:c8b6:a7d8:c897:cd8f/64 Scope:Global
          UP BROADCAST RUNNING MULTICAST  MTU:1500  Metric:1
          RX packets:18607 errors:0 dropped:0 overruns:0 frame:0
          TX packets:8644 errors:0 dropped:0 overruns:0 carrier:0
          collisions:0 txqueuelen:1000
          RX bytes:2282499 (2.1 MiB)  TX bytes:1025772 (1001.7 KiB)

lo        Link encap:Local Loopback
          inet addr:127.0.0.1  Mask:255.0.0.0
          inet6 addr: ::1/128 Scope:Host
          UP LOOPBACK RUNNING  MTU:65536  Metric:1
          RX packets:101 errors:0 dropped:0 overruns:0 frame:0
          TX packets:101 errors:0 dropped:0 overruns:0 carrier:0
          collisions:0 txqueuelen:1
          RX bytes:9505 (9.2 KiB)  TX bytes:9505 (9.2 KiB)

wlan0     Link encap:Ethernet  HWaddr b8:27:eb:c3:99:0f
          inet addr:192.168.0.200  Bcast:192.168.0.255  Mask:255.255.255.0
          inet6 addr: fe80::ba27:ebff:fec3:990f/64 Scope:Link
          inet6 addr: 2600:8804:1e80:6e30:ba27:ebff:fec3:990f/64 Scope:Global
          UP BROADCAST RUNNING MULTICAST  MTU:1500  Metric:1
          RX packets:58092 errors:0 dropped:48756 overruns:0 frame:0
          TX packets:830 errors:0 dropped:0 overruns:0 carrier:0
          collisions:0 txqueuelen:1000
          RX bytes:9698158 (9.2 MiB)  TX bytes:90407 (88.2 KiB)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, if you want to get your internal ip address, you can search for the value after &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;inet addr:my.ip.add.ress&lt;/code&gt;. Search for it like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ ifconfig | grep &quot;inet addr:&quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This address you can type into any computer attatched to the local network and be able to access your server’s site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But what if you want for everyone to be able to access your website?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To do this you have to use something called &lt;strong&gt;port forwarding&lt;/strong&gt;. Port forwarding makes it so that when a request comes in to your router on a certain port, it can be redirected to a local computer. We will make it so that when you type in the browser &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;my.routers.ip.address:8090&lt;/code&gt; you will be able to access your website from anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;port-forwarding&quot;&gt;Port forwarding&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Log into your router’s configuration page. To do this, go into your browser and type in the ip for the page. Usually the ip is something like this: &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;192.168.0.1&lt;/code&gt;. If it is not that, search the web for your router’s configuration page address and type that as the url.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;When you get to the login page you will need to input the username and password. Usually, the username is &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;admin&lt;/code&gt; and the password is &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;password&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;When you are in, navigate to a tab called firewalls, and find a page called &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;port forwarding/virtual servers&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;To add a port forwarding rule, click &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;add&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fill out all of the ports with this number: &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;8090&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;em&gt;NOTE: I would normally use port &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;80&lt;/code&gt; so people would not have to bother with typing the port more than once, but some companies (like cox) do not allow forwarding on 80&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;For the IP address, put in the ip for your raspberry pi (inet addr: &lt;strong&gt;my.r.pi’s.ip&lt;/strong&gt;). We found our pi’s ip in the previous section.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;For the option to use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;TCP&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;UDP&lt;/code&gt;, or &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;BOTH&lt;/code&gt;, choose &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;BOTH&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click the add button&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have now successfully added port forwarding for your website!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Scribble, a Jekyll theme</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/03/11/scribble-the-jekyll-theme/"/>
   <updated>2017-03-11T18:06:52-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/03/11/scribble-the-jekyll-theme</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Instruction as follows. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;get-started&quot;&gt;Get started&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/muan/scribble/fork&quot;&gt;Fork the repository&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Clone the repository: &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;git clone https://github.com/username/scribble&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundle install&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Run Jekyll: &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve -w&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Go to http://localhost:4000 for your site.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;make-it-yours&quot;&gt;Make it yours&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Edit &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt;, adn then rerun &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve -w&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Change &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;about.md&lt;/code&gt; for blog intro&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;For domain settings see &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.github.com/articles/setting-up-a-custom-domain-with-pages&quot;&gt;the guide from GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/muan/scribble&quot; class=&quot;pa3 tc ba br2 db&quot;&gt;Get it on GitHub ♥&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-end&quot;&gt;The end&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like it? &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/muanchiou&quot;&gt;Tell me&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
Problem? &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/muan/scribble&quot;&gt;Use GitHub Issues&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Introduction</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2016/01/03/introduction/"/>
   <updated>2016-01-03T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2016/01/03/introduction</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Strange Case of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde&lt;/em&gt; tells the story of a lawyer investigating the connection of two persons, Dr. Henry Jekyll and Mr. Edward Hyde. Chief among the novel’s supporting cast is a man by the name of Mr. Poole, Dr. Jekyll’s loyal butler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poole is the butler for &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;, the static site generator. It’s designed and developed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mdo&quot;&gt;@mdo&lt;/a&gt; to provide a clear and concise foundational setup for any Jekyll site. It does so by furnishing a full vanilla Jekyll install with example layouts, pages, posts, and styles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are currently three themes built on Poole:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://hyde.getpoole.com&quot;&gt;Hyde&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://lanyon.getpoole.com&quot;&gt;Lanyon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://enfield.getpoole.com&quot;&gt;Enfield&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more and contribute on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/poole&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;whats-included&quot;&gt;What’s included&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poole is a streamlined Jekyll site designed and built as a foundation for building more meaningful themes. Poole, and every theme built on it like this one, includes the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Complete Jekyll setup included (layouts, config, &lt;a href=&quot;/404.html&quot;&gt;404&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/atom.xml&quot;&gt;RSS feed&lt;/a&gt;, posts, and &lt;a href=&quot;/about&quot;&gt;example page&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile friendly design and development&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Easily scalable text and component sizing with &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;rem&lt;/code&gt; units in the CSS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Support for a wide gamut of HTML elements&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Related posts (time-based, because Jekyll) below each post&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Syntax highlighting, courtesy Jekyll’s built-in support for Rouge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional features are available in individual themes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;browser-support&quot;&gt;Browser support&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poole and its themes are by preference a forward-thinking project. In addition to the latest versions of Chrome, Safari (mobile and desktop), and Firefox, it is only compatible with Internet Explorer 9 and above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;download&quot;&gt;Download&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These themes are developed on and hosted with GitHub. Head to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/poole&quot;&gt;GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt; for downloads, bug reports, and features requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Example content</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2016/01/02/example-content/"/>
   <updated>2016-01-02T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2016/01/02/example-content</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;message&quot;&gt;
  Howdy! This is an example blog post that shows several types of HTML content supported in this theme.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;dis parturient montes&lt;/a&gt;, nascetur ridiculus mus. &lt;em&gt;Aenean eu leo quam.&lt;/em&gt; Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis. Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo. Nullam id dolor id nibh ultricies vehicula ut id elit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Etiam porta &lt;strong&gt;sem malesuada magna&lt;/strong&gt; mollis euismod. Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum. Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;inline-html-elements&quot;&gt;Inline HTML elements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTML defines a long list of available inline tags, a complete list of which can be found on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTML/Element&quot;&gt;Mozilla Developer Network&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To bold text&lt;/strong&gt;, use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;To italicize text&lt;/em&gt;, use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Abbreviations, like &lt;abbr title=&quot;HyperText Markup Langage&quot;&gt;HTML&lt;/abbr&gt; should use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;abbr&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;, with an optional &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;title&lt;/code&gt; attribute for the full phrase.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Citations, like &lt;cite&gt;— Mark otto&lt;/cite&gt;, should use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;cite&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;Deleted&lt;/del&gt; text should use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;del&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;ins&gt;inserted&lt;/ins&gt; text should use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;ins&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Superscript &lt;sup&gt;text&lt;/sup&gt; uses &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and subscript &lt;sub&gt;text&lt;/sub&gt; uses &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;sub&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of these elements are styled by browsers with few modifications on our part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;Footnotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Footnotes are supported as part of the Markdown syntax. Here’s one in action. Clicking this number&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:fn-sample_footnote&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:fn-sample_footnote&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; will lead you to a footnote. The syntax looks like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot; data-lang=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Clicking this number[^fn-sample_footnote]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each footnote needs the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;^fn-&lt;/code&gt; prefix and a unique ID to be referenced for the footnoted content. The syntax for that list looks something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot; data-lang=&quot;text&quot;&gt;[^fn-sample_footnote]: Handy! Now click the return link to go back.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can place the footnoted content wherever you like. Markdown parsers should properly place it at the bottom of the post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;heading&quot;&gt;Heading&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;code&quot;&gt;Code&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inline code is available with the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;code&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; element. Snippets of multiple lines of code are supported through Pygments. Longer lines will automatically scroll horizontally when needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-js&quot; data-lang=&quot;js&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Example can be run directly in your JavaScript console
&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Create a function that takes two arguments and returns the sum of those arguments
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;kd&quot;&gt;var&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;adder&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;Function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;a&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;b&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;return a + b&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Call the function
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;adder&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// &amp;gt; 8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may also optionally show code snippets with line numbers. Add &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;linenos&lt;/code&gt; to the Pygments tags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-js&quot; data-lang=&quot;js&quot;&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
8
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Example can be run directly in your JavaScript console
&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Create a function that takes two arguments and returns the sum of those arguments
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;kd&quot;&gt;var&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;adder&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;Function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;a&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;b&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;return a + b&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Call the function
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;adder&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// &amp;gt; 8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur. Etiam porta sem malesuada magna mollis euismod. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gists-via-github-pages&quot;&gt;Gists via GitHub Pages&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo. Donec sed odio dui.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;https://gist.github.com/13f94b734a4ddb132735.js?file=gist.md&quot;&gt; &lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aenean eu leo quam. Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Donec sed odio dui. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lists&quot;&gt;Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur. Etiam porta sem malesuada magna mollis euismod. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Donec id elit non mi porta gravida at eget metus.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donec ullamcorper nulla non metus auctor fringilla. Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Maecenas sed diam eget risus varius blandit sit amet non magna.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
  &lt;dt&gt;HyperText Markup Language (HTML)&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;The language used to describe and define the content of a Web page&lt;/dd&gt;

  &lt;dt&gt;Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;Used to describe the appearance of Web content&lt;/dd&gt;

  &lt;dt&gt;JavaScript (JS)&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;The programming language used to build advanced Web sites and applications&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Integer posuere erat a ante venenatis dapibus posuere velit aliquet. Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;images&quot;&gt;Images&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quisque consequat sapien eget quam rhoncus, sit amet laoreet diam tempus. Aliquam aliquam metus erat, a pulvinar turpis suscipit at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/800x400&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; title=&quot;Large example image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/400x200&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; title=&quot;Medium example image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/200x200&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; title=&quot;Small example image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Upvotes&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Downvotes&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tfoot&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Totals&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;21&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;23&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tfoot&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alice&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;11&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bob&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Charlie&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nullam id dolor id nibh ultricies vehicula ut id elit. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to see something else added? &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/poole/issues/new&quot;&gt;Open an issue.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:fn-sample_footnote&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Handy! Now click the return link to go back. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:fn-sample_footnote&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What's Jekyll?</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2016/01/01/whats-jekyll/"/>
   <updated>2016-01-01T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2016/01/01/whats-jekyll</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is a static site generator, an open-source tool for creating simple yet powerful websites of all shapes and sizes. From &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll/blob/master/README.markdown&quot;&gt;the project’s readme&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a simple, blog aware, static site generator. It takes a template directory […] and spits out a complete, static website suitable for serving with Apache or your favorite web server. This is also the engine behind GitHub Pages, which you can use to host your project’s page or blog right here from GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s an immensely useful tool. Find out more by &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;visiting the project on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Lorem Ipsum Dolor Sit Amet Consectetur Elit</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/05/06/more-post/"/>
   <updated>2013-05-06T10:27:31-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/05/06/more-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am a placeholder post. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Aenean commodo ligula eget dolor. Aenean massa. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Abore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;– Akei Yue&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;List with code&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; not highlighted
 multi line
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;List with code&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;language-javascript highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;kd&quot;&gt;var&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;dom&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;document&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;getElementById&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'boom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;dom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Aenean commodo ligula eget dolor. Aenean massa. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Donec quam felis, ultricies nec, pellentesque eu, pretium quis, sem. Nulla consequat massa quis enim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Aenean commodo ligula eget dolor. Aenean massa. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-html highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;dialog&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;header&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Headsup&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/header&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna.&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;button&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;type=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;button&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;class=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;js-close-dialog&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Close&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/button&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/dialog&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
